Guide to the Rudolf Carnap Papers, 1904-2007 ASP.1974.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Supplementary Carnap Material with Varied Provenance, 1913-2007; XXVI.
  - Letters from Wilhelm Essler to Carnap, and Correspondence Pertaining to Commemorative Activities following Carnap's Death; donated by Professor Wilhelm Essler, 9 items, 1969-1971 (Box 115, Folder 11)
  - "Carnap's Letter to Frau Lila": A copy of a typed letter from Carnap to an unidentified Frau Lila, mainly discussing personal matters, and a copy of the title page of Wissenschaftliche Weltauffassung: Der Wiener Kreis with handwritten notes by Carnap and another hand; 3 items, 1929 (Box 115, Folder 12)
  - Transcription of a Tape-Recorded Book List for the Rudolf Carnap Papers. Books owned by Carnap enumerated in a tape recording and subsequent typed transcription; 2 items. (Box 115, Folder 13)
  - Photographic Negatives of Original Photos from the Carnap Papers. Negatives produced at the request of various researchers during recent years; 44 items. (Box 115, Folder 14)
  - Transcription of Carnap's Shorthand Annotations in His Books. Transcription of Carnap's shorthand annotations in books of his library, created at the request of researchers; 1 item. (Box 115, Folder 15)
  - Carlos Ulises Moulines Documents: One circular letter by Rudolf Carnap with handwritten, dictated notes to Professor Rolf George; one handwritten letter in German by Moulines to Rudolf Carnap, with two enclosed, handwritten essays in German by Moulines entitled "Konstitution der eigenpsychischen Gegenstände" and "Konstitution der Zeit im Gebiet des Eigenpsychischen;" 3 items, 1968 (Box 115, Folder 16)
  - Story by Peter Achinstein about a Meeting with Carnap, L.J. Savage and Others during the Mid-1960's. 1 item, 2007 (Box 115, Folder 17)
  - Honorary Doctoral Degree from Harvard University, September 18, 1936 (Box 116)
- Name Index, XXVII.
  The Name Index gives the user a broad picture of the many people Carnap knew or with whom he corresponded from all over the world and throughout his life. The aim of this index is to make the Rudolf Carnap Papers more accessible to scholars. To do this we have compiled this list of names from Carnap's correspondence, notes he made on people or their works, clippings which Carnap saved from magazines and newspapers, and so on. The list is limited to the names of people, i.e., philosophers, publishers, friends, students, and others, showing Carnap's wide-ranging interests and interactions.
  The names are arranged alphabeticaly. Beside each name is a number in parantheses which indicates the number of items the name occurs in the specific file.
  - Aaron, Benjamin (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Abbanano, Nicola (Box 27, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Abel, Elie (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Abell, Georga (Box 95, Folder 9, Item 2)
  - Achinstein, Peter (Box 84, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Achinstein, Peter (Box 90, Folder 75, Item 3)
  - Ackerman (Box 81, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Adams, Ernest (Box 84, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Addams, Jane (Box 90, Folder 14, Item 4)
  - Agassi, Joseph (Box 88, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Aqvist, Lennart (Box 95, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Adukiewicz, K. (Box 28, Folder 1, Item 5)
  - Akiba, Ben (Box 79, Folder 35, Item 4)
  - Albert, Anthony J. (Box 83, Folder 36, Item 3)
  - Albritton, Rogers (Box 88, Folder 35, Item 2)
  - Albritton, Rogers (Box 88, Folder 85, Item 2)
  - Albritton, Rogers (Box 90, Folder 73, Item 1)
  - Alexander, Gavin (Box 27, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Allen, R.B. (Box 85, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Allen, R.B. (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Alpert, Harry (Box 91, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Alsop, Joseph (Box 94, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Alston, William P. (Box 90, Folder 69, Item 2)
  - Altman, Julius (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Altman, Zelena G. (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Altrichter, Fernc (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Ambrose, Warren (Box 90, Folder 47, Item 5)
  - Amburgery, Nancy (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - Ammermann, Robert (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 3)
  - Anderson, Alan Ross (Box 102, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Anderson, Alan Ross (Box 102, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Anderson, Fay (Box 80, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Anderson, Fay (Box 91, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Andics-Karikas, Margarethe (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 7)
  - Angell, Richard B. (Box 27, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Angstrom, Martha (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Apostel, Leo (Box 27, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Apostel, Leo (Box 88, Folder 1, Item 2)
  - Arlt, Gustave O. (Box 80, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Arlt, Gustave O. (Box 85, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Arlt, Gustave O. (Box 88, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Arlt, Gustave O. (Box 90, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - Armstrong, Robert P. (Box 91, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Arnone, M.S. (Box 94, Folder 22, Item 2)
  - Arrow, Kenneth J. (Box 84, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Aschenbrenner, Karl (Box 85, Folder 48, Item 1)
  - Aschenbrenner, Karl (Box 90, Folder 70, Item 7)
  - Atamian, Alice (Box 27, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Atkin, Gene (Box 102, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Atkinson, R. (Box 85, Folder 58, Item 1)
  - Auld, William (Box 95, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Ayer, A.J. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Ayer, A.J. (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Bachmann, Friedrich (Box 28, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Baculewski, Jan (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Badenius, Duncan (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 4)
  - Bailiff, John D. (Box 85, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Bailyn, Bernard (Box 80, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Bakonyi, Stefano (Box 95, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Barakin, Edward W. (Box 84, Folder 42, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Shulmith (Box 102, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 80, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 84, Folder 5, Item 5)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 84, Folder 47, Item 4)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 84, Folder 57, Item 2)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 102, Folder 1, Item 32)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 102, Folder 2, Item 135)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 107, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Bar-Hillel, Yehoshua (Box 109, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Barney, Emily F. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Bar-On, A.Z. (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 3)
  - Barrett, Robert B. (Box 91, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Barrett, William (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Bartlett, George Robert (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Bartlett, George Robert (Box 102, Folder 47, Item 2)
  - Bartley, W.W. (Box 88, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Bashir, M. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Basri, Saul A. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 6)
  - Basri, Saul A. (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 5)
  - Batens, Diderik (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Battaglia, Felice (Box 88, Folder 80, Item 3)
  - Bauch, Bruno (Box 28, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Bavink, B. (Box 28, Folder 4, Item 5)
  - Baylis, Charles A. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Beals, Carleton (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Bean and Laing (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Bean, D.P. (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Beard, Robert W. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 9)
  - Beard, Robert W. (Box 27, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Beauvoirs, Simon De (Box 90, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Beck, Robert N. (Box 88, Folder 77, Item 3)
  - Becker, Albr. (Box 25, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Beckwith, Burnham (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Behmann, Heinrich (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Behmann, Heinrich (Box 28, Folder 6, Item 12)
  - Behmann, Heinrich (Box 28, Folder 7, Item 4)
  - Behmann, Heinrich (Box 89, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Behmann, Heinrich (Box 89, Folder 18, Item 2)
  - Behmann, Heinrich (Box 81, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Beil, Myron M. (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Belfrage, Cedric (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Bell, Clifford (Box 27, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Belser, Joseph (Box 90, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Benacerraf, Paul (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 4)
  - Benary, Wilhelm (Box 110, Folder 5, Item 104)
  - Benjamin, Walter (Box 81, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Bennett, Michael (Box 80, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Benoist, Alain De (Box 80, Folder 1, Item 3)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 81, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 85, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 87, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 88, Folder 3, Item 12)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 91, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Benson, Arthur (Box 91, Folder 51, Item 5)
  - Bergmann, Eva (Box 102, Folder 32, Item 3)
  - Bergmann, Gustav (Box 80, Folder 15, Item 5)
  - Bergmann, Hugo (Box 102, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Berka, Karel (Box 90, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Bernard, [ ] (Box 80, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Bernau, Gustav (Box 85, Folder 11, Item 3)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 28, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Bernays, Paul (Box 88, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Bernheim, Kurt (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Bernstein, Moro (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Bernstein, Moro (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Bertschi, Ernst (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 3)
  - Beth, E.W. (Box 88, Folder 5, Item 7)
  - Beth, E.W. (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Beth, E.W. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Beth, E.W. (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Beth, E.W. (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Beth, E.W. (Box 109, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Bigger, Charles P. (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Birgenfelds, Ludwig (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Birmann, Katja (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Birnbaum, Allan (Box 84, Folder 8, Item 2)
  - Blacet, Francis (Box 90, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Black, Max (Box 80, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Black, Max (Box 94, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Blackwell, Basil (Box 85, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Blackwell, Kenneth (Box 90, Folder 6, Item 2)
  - Blanchard, Brand (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Blaustein, Norman (Box 91, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Ernst (Box 90, Folder 53, Item 1)
  - Bloch, Ernst (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Blomberg (Box 110, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Blumberg, Albert E. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 3)
  - Blumberg, Albert E. (Box 88, Folder 6, Item 5)
  - Bochenski, J.M. (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Bochenski, J.M. (Box 88, Folder 7, Item 6)
  - Bochenski, J.M. (Box 21, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Bockman, Pauline (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 88, Folder 8, Item 35)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 88, Folder 9, Item 8)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 91, Folder 15, Item 2)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 91, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 102, Folder 3, Item 18)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 107, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Herbert G. (Box 109, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Bohnert, Rudolf (Box 88, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Boll, Marcel (Box 91, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Boltzmann, Ludwig (Box 81, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Bond, E.J (Box 27, Folder 36, Item 2)
  - Bonno, G. (Box 85, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Borel, E. (Box 81, Folder 44, Item 1)
  - Bostain, Mary W. (Box 91, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Bostain, Mary W. (Box 91, Folder 5, Item 6)
  - Bostain, Mary W. (Box 91, Folder 6, Item 3)
  - Boyer, Edna D. (Box 72, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Bozbena, Rudolf (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Bradbury, Ray (Box 90, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Braithwaite, R.B. (Box 90, Folder 31, Item 1)
  - Bram, Leila D. (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 7)
  - Braoml, Mariou (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Braun, G. (Box 110, Folder 5, Item 19)
  - Bray, Mary (Box 95, Folder 29, Item 19)
  - Bressan, Aldo (Box 88, Folder 10, Item 22)
  - Bridgman, P.W. (Box 102, Folder 38, Item 7)
  - Briggs, Grace A. (Box 85, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Briones, Gillermo (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Britt, Patricia Marie (Box 85, Folder 43, Item 1)
  - Brod, Masc (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 2)
  - Brody, Boruch A. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 4)
  - Brokaw, Miriam (Box 27, Folder 60, Item 2)
  - Bronstein, Daniel J. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Brooks, Ernest Jr. (Box 90, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Brouwer (Box 81, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Brown, James Cooke (Box 95, Folder 24, Item 7)
  - Brown, Peter (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Brown, Peter (Box 90, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Brown, Stuart (Box 27, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Brown, Yvonne (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Brugmann, Karl (Box 81, Folder 49, Item 1)
  - Brunner, Karl (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Brushlinsky, V. (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Brushlinsky, V. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Brushlinsky, V. (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Brushlinsky, V. (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Brushlinsky, V. (Box 109, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Brutian, George (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Brutian, George (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Bryant, Lynwood (Box 82, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Bryant, Lynwood (Box 82, Folder 15, Item 14)
  - Bubbe, Walter (Box 89, Folder 63, Item 1)
  - Buchler, Karl (Box 110, Folder 3, Item 2)
  - Buck, Roger C. (Box 27, Folder 2, Item 2)
  - Buick, Carole (Box 85, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Bullock, Theodore H. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Bullock, Theodore H. (Box 85, Folder 33, Item 3)
  - Bulloff, Jack J. (Box 27, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Bulloff, Jack J. (Box 88, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Bulygin, Eugenio (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Buge, Mario (Box 88, Folder 12, Item 7)
  - Buge, Mario (Box 89, Folder 52, Item 9)
  - Burchett, Wilfred (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Burdick, Eugene (Box 94, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Burkamp, Wilhelm (Box 28, Folder 8, Item 4)
  - Burks, Arthur W. (Box 84, Folder 11, Item 10)
  - Burks, Arthur W. (Box 94, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Burks, Arthur W. (Box 107, Folder 7, Item 3)
  - Burks, Arthur W. (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Burrill, Donald (Box 85, Folder 47, Item 4)
  - Butrick, Richard (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Butterfield, Victor L. (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Buzi, Fernendo Vidal (Box 27, Folder 38, Item 1)
  - Bynum, Terrell Ward (Box 88, Folder 13, Item 9)
  - Byrne, Jerome C. (Box 85, Folder 32, Item 1)
  - Cain, Kay Ellen (Box 88, Folder 75, Item 1)
  - Cain, Kay Ellen (Box 89, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Calbhenn, Theo Bernd (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Callaghan, William J. (Box 88, Folder 8, Item 3)
  - Calhum, Brook (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Calvache, Rene (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Cameron, Gordon B. (Box 85, Folder 34, Item 1)
  - Cap, F. (Box 90, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Capek, Milic (Box 94, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Capouya, Emile (Box 27, Folder 61, Item 3)
  - Carnap, Anna (Box 102, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Hanniliese (Hanna Thost) (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 19)
  - Carnap, Hanniliese (Hanna Thost) (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Carnap, Hanniliese (Hanna Thost) (Box 21, Folder 64, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Hanniliese (Hanna Thost) (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 30)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 90, Folder 68, Item 2)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 91, Folder 7, Item 5)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 91, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 3)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 91, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 91, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 102, Folder 27, Item 3)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Carnap, Elizabeth (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Carroll, Mark (Box 27, Folder 56, Item 1)
  - Carroll, Sandra (Box 27, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Carruth, Hayden (Box 85, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Carstens, Bea (Box 88, Folder 70, Item 1)
  - Carter, John G. (Box 27, Folder 58, Item 1)
  - Cauman, Leigh S. (Box 91, Folder 13, Item 1)
  - Cell, Edward C. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 4)
  - Champawat, Marayan (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Champawat, Marayan (Box 85, Folder 45, Item 3)
  - Champawat, Marayan (Box 107, Folder 6, Item 1)
  - Champawat, Marayan (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 1)
  - Chang, C.C. (Box 85, Folder 40, Item 1)
  - Charlesworth, M.J. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Charner, [ ] (Box 80, Folder 73, Item 1)
  - Chappell, Vere (Box 27, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Chatalian, George (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Chesnut, Charles (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 3)
  - Chavalier, Haakom (Box 88, Folder 79, Item 1)
  - Chomsky, Naom (Box 88, Folder 14, Item 3)
  - Chomsky, Naom (Box 94, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Christenson, Jon D. (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 3)
  - Christiansen, Broder (Box 28, Folder 10, Item 7)
  - Christiansen, Broder (Box 28, Folder 11, Item 4)
  - Christiansen, Broder (Box 89, Folder 63, Item 1)
  - Christiansen, Broder (Box 102, Folder 26, Item 7)
  - Christiansen, Broder (Box 21, Folder 74, Item 4)
  - Chung, Lung-ock (Box 27, Folder 3, Item 4)
  - Church, Alonzo (Box 85, Folder 41, Item 1)
  - Church, Alonzo (Box 88, Folder 15, Item 11)
  - Church, Alonzo (Box 89, Folder 7, Item 1)
  - Church, Alonzo (Box 89, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Churchman, West (Box 84, Folder 13, Item 3)
  - Chwistek (Box 81, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Ciecka, Mary (Box 85, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Cirker, Hayward (Box 27, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Cirker, Hayward (Box 27, Folder 55, Item 20)
  - Cirker, Hayward (Box 85, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Cirker, Hayward (Box 85, Folder 12, Item 13)
  - Cirker, Hayward (Box 90, Folder 80, Item 1)
  - Clarke, Francis P. (Box 81, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Clarke, Francis P. (Box 90, Folder 12, Item 2)
  - Cocchiarella, Nino B. (Box 85, Folder 46, Item 1)
  - Coffel, [ ] (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Cohen, L.J. (Box 27, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 80, Folder 17, Item 4)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 88, Folder 16, Item 16)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 88, Folder 73, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 89, Folder 26, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 91, Folder 30, Item 19)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 102, Folder 48, Item 2)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robert (Box 109, Folder 20, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Robin (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Cohen, Ronald (Box 80, Folder 1, Item 1)
  - Compton, Boyd (Box 27, Folder 37, Item 1)
  - Connelly, John J. (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Costantini, Domenico (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 7)
  - Costantini, Domenico (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Cook, Fred J. (Box 94, Folder 20, Item 2)
  - Copeland, Prof. [ ] (Box 84, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Copi, Irving (Box 27, Folder 3, Item 7)
  - Copi, Irving (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Copi, Irving (Box 88, Folder 18, Item 8)
  - Corbett, Paul (Box 85, Folder 10, Item 1)
  - Cocoran, John (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 4)
  - Corley, James H. (Box 91, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Cosgrove, Harrison (Box 90, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Cosgrove, Lucille D. (Box 90, Folder 54, Item 1)
  - Costas, Enrique (Box 27, Folder 39, Item 1)
  - Courtenaye, Juanita (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 5)
  - Coustal, R. (Box 95, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Cowan, Paul (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Cox, Sandra (Box 27, Folder 36, Item 1)
  - Craig, William (Box 88, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Craig, William (Box 90, Folder 54, Item 3)
  - Creary, Lewis G. (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Creary, Lewis G. (Box 88, Folder 20, Item 3)
  - Crescini, Angelo (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 9)
  - Cressey, Donald R. (Box 27, Folder 18, Item 1)
  - Cristofaro Sandrini, Maria-Grazia De (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Crowe, Donald W. (Box 84, Folder 68, Item 1)
  - Cutler, Preston S. (Box 90, Folder 56, Item 1)
  - Czapski, Hans (Box 102, Folder 28, Item 1)
  - Czermely, D. (Box 28, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Czuczka, George T. (Box 85, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Dalsgrad-Hansen, P. (Box 27, Folder 30, Item 1)
  - Daniels, Victor (Box 27, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Danielzik, Uta (Box 88, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Dantzig, D. Van (Box 110, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Dantzig, D. Van (Box 81, Folder 65, Item 1)
  - Darbon, [ ] (Box 29, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - Darlington, Jared L. (Box 27, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Daum, Florence (Box 27, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 27, Folder 4, Item 4)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 84, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 91, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 109, Folder 12, Item 1)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 109, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 109, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 109, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - Davidson, Donald (Box 109, Folder 27, Item 1)
  - Davis, Angela (Box 94, Folder 9, Item 9)
  - Davis, Martin (Box 94, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Davis, Robert L. (Box 84, Folder 68, Item 12)
  - Davis, Sydney C. (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Davis, Virgil (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 1)
  - De Boer, Jesse (Box 90, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - De Finetti, Bruno (Box 81, Folder 65, Item 1)
  - De Finetti, Bruno (Box 84, Folder 16, Item 2)
  - De Finetti, Bruno (Box 84, Folder 50, Item 1)
  - DeHann, Richard (Box 85, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - DeHann, Richard (Box 88, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Delius, Harald (Box 88, Folder 21, Item 1)
  - Delsasso, Leo P. (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 1)
  - Dellinger, Dave (Box 94, Folder 19, Item 1)
  - Dellinger, Dave (Box 94, Folder 24, Item 1)
  - De Marzio, Giulio (Box 88, Folder 80, Item 8)
  - Demes, William R. (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Dennes, William R. (Box 85, Folder 29, Item 5)
  - Dennes, William R. (Box 90, Folder 70, Item 1)
  - Deutscher, Isaac (Box 94, Folder 14, Item 1)
  - Dewey, John (Box 102, Folder 39, Item 12)
  - Diamond, Basil (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 4)
  - Dickson, Harald (Box 27, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Dijkman, J.G. (Box 27, Folder 29, Item 1)
  - Dingler, Hugo (Box 28, Folder 12, Item 9)
  - Dochx, S. (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Dochx, S. (Box 90, Folder 33, Item 26)
  - Dochx, S. (Box 21, Folder 71, Item 3)
  - Dommeyer, Frederick G. (Box 85, Folder 55, Item 1)
  - Dommeyer, Frederick G. (Box 90, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Domotor, Zoltan (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 2)
  - Doneis, Armin F. (Box 95, Folder 21, Item 3)
  - Doob, J.L. (Box 79, Folder 17, Item 2)
  - Dorpfeld, Fritz (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 4)
  - Dorpfeld, Wilhelm (Box 102, Folder 30, Item 4)
  - Douglas, Richard M. (Box 84, Folder 53, Item 3)
  - Doyle, Pete (Box 83, Folder 33, Item 4)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 27, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 82, Folder 23, Item 2)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 83, Folder 3, Item 3)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 83, Folder 24, Item 2)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 83, Folder 25, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 91, Folder 2, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 91, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 91, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 91, Folder 7, Item 2)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 91, Folder 8, Item 1)
  - Drake, Doris (Box 21, Folder 69, Item 1)
  - Drummond, William J. (Box 94, Folder 9, Item 1)
  - Dubislav, Walter (Box 28, Folder 13, Item 10)
  - Duckles, Ed (Box 88, Folder 51, Item 10)
  - Ducrot, O. (Box 27, Folder 32, Item 2)
  - Durr, Karl (Box 27, Folder 4, Item 3)
  - Durr, Karl (Box 28, Folder 14, Item 2)
  - Durr, Karl (Box 21, Folder 76, Item 1)
  - Earman, John (Box 80, Folder 4, Item 2)
  - Earman, John (Box 88, Folder 22, Item 1)
  - Economos, Judith (Box 90, Folder 56, Item 1)
  - Eckert (Box 81, Folder 11, Item 1)
  - Edel, Abraham (Box 27, Folder 5, Item 2)
  - Edmundson, H.P. (Box 27, Folder 26, Item 3)
  - Edwards, Paul (Box 81, Folder 9, Item 28)
  - Edwards, Paul (Box 88, Folder 23, Item 6)
  - Edwards, Paul (Box 88, Folder 77, Item 1)
  - Egenhofer, Albert W. (Box 94, Folder 4, Item 1)
  - Einstein, Albert (Box 102, Folder 40, Item 8)
  - Eklund, H. (Box 28, Folder 15, Item 1)
  - Ekstein, Rudolf (Box 27, Folder 26, Item 6)
  - Ekstein, Rudolf (Box 80, Folder 5, Item 1)
  - Ekstein, Rudolf (Box 102, Folder 17, Item 1)
  - Ekstein, Ruth and Rubin (Box 80, Folder 3, Item 1)
  - Ellis, A.C. (Box 102, Folder 52, Item 1)
  - Elwyn, Sister Mary (Box 27, Folder 26, Item 3)
  - Enescu, Gheorghe (Box 27, Folder 26, Item 2)
  - Engel, F. (Box 28, Folder 16, Item 1)
  - English, Maurice (Box 29, Folder 10, Item 1)